<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Countryprofile</string>

    <string-array name="country">
        <item>Bangladesh</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>Argentina</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Belzium</item>
        <item>Chilie</item>
        <item>Iraq</item>
        <item>Fizi</item>
        <item>Canada</item>
        <item>Egypt</item>
        <item>Crotetia</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Usa</item>


    </string-array>
    <string name="altitle">Countryprofile</string>
    <string name="almasg">Hey! Do you want to Exit!!??</string>
    <string name="bdpro">

        Bangladesh is one of the worlds most densely populated countries, with its people crammed into a delta of rivers that empties into the Bay of Bengal.
        Poverty is deep and widespread, but Bangladesh has in recent years reduced population growth and improved health and education.
        Formerly East Pakistan, Bangladesh came into being only in 1971, when the two parts of Pakistan split after a bitter war which drew in neighbouring India.
        Bangladesh spent 15 years under military rule and, although democracy was restored in 1990, the political scene remains volatile.
        Islamist extremism has been rising in the usually tolerant country.
        The low-lying country is vulnerable to flooding and cyclones, and stands to be badly affected by any rises in sea levels.


    </string>


    <string name="pakpro">

        The Muslim-majority state of Pakistan was born out of the partition of the Indian sub-continent in 1947, and has faced both domestic political upheavals and regional confrontations.
        Created to meet the demands of Indian Muslims for their own homeland, Pakistan was originally made up of two parts.
        The east wing - present-day Bangladesh - is on the Bay of Bengal bordering India and Burma. The west wing - present-day Pakistan - stretches from the Himalayas down to the Arabian Sea.
        The break-up of the two wings came in 1971 when the Bengali-speaking east wing seceded with help from India.



    </string>

    <string name="indiapro">



        India is the worlds largest democracy and according to UN estimates, its population is expected to overtake Chinas in 2028 to become the worlds most populous nation.
        As a rising economic powerhouse and nuclear-armed state, India has emerged as an important regional power.
        But it is also tackling huge, social, economic and environmental problems.
        Home to some of the worlds most ancient surviving civilizations, the Indian subcontinent - from the mountainous Afghan frontier to the jungles of Burma - is both vast and diverse in terms of its people, language and cultural traditions.


    </string>
    <string name="Argentina">

        Argentina is the worlds largest democracy and according to UN estimates, its population is expected to overtake Chinas in 2028 to become the worlds most populous nation.
        As a rising economic powerhouse and nuclear-armed state, India has emerged as an important regional power.
        But it is also tackling huge, social, economic and environmental problems.
        Home to some of the worlds most ancient surviving civilizations, the Indian subcontinent - from the mountainous Afghan frontier to the jungles of Burma - is both vast and diverse in terms of its people, language and cultural traditions.



    </string>

    <string name="Brazil">

        Brazil is the worlds largest democracy and according to UN estimates, its population is expected to overtake Chinas in 2028 to become the worlds most populous nation.
        As a rising economic powerhouse and nuclear-armed state, India has emerged as an important regional power.
        But it is also tackling huge, social, economic and environmental problems.
        Home to some of the worlds most ancient surviving civilizations, the Indian subcontinent - from the mountainous Afghan frontier to the jungles of Burma - is both vast and diverse in terms of its people, language and cultural traditions.



    </string>
</resources>
